A love story, unequaled.
Bridegroom is a documentary, drama film directed by Linda Bloodworth-Thomason.
A documentary that tells the emotional journey of Shane and Tom, two young men in a loving and committed
relationship — a relationship that was cut tragically short by a misstep off the side of a roof.
Himself (archive footage), played by Thomas Bridegroom.
Himself, played by Shane Bitney Crone.
Herself, played by Cindy Bitney.
Himself, played by David Crone.
Herself, played by Lizzy Mohl.
Herself, played by Judy Crone.
Bridegroom (full title: Bridegroom: A Love Story, Unequaled) is a 2013 American documentary film about the
relationship between two young gay men, produced and directed by Linda Bloodworth-Thomason.
Bridegroom premiered at the 2013 Tribeca Film Festival on April 23, 2013, and attracted further press coverage
because its premiere screening at the festival was introduced by former President Bill Clinton.
The film won the festival's Audience Award for Best Documentary Film.
The film jointly received the 2014 GLAAD Media Award for
Outstanding Documentary alongside Call Me Kuchu.
The film explores themes of marriage crisis,
marriage, equality, love, death of lover.
The tone is emotional.